http://www.biomin.net/privacy-policy/

Zum InhaltZur HauptnavigationPrivacy Policy(a) General InformationThis policy is to be read in conjunction with the terms and conditions of acceptable use and the registration/membership terms which apply to this site. The processing of your personal data takes place only in accordance with the valid data protection regulations.(b) Controller of data processingERBER AG Erber Campus 1 3131 Getzersdorf, AustriaIf you have data protection questions, you can reach us at dataprotection(at)erber-group.net.(c) Processing of personal data when using the websiteAs far as possible, the use of the services offered on our website takes place without the processing of personal data. However, the use of certain services offered on our website requires the processing of personal data. Before using certain services (eg applicant platform; click here for more details on the use of Cookies) and the associated processing of your personal data, you will be asked to give your explicit consent to the processing of your data for the purposes specified in the privacy statement.BY TICKING THE BOX OF THE STATEMENT OF CONSENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY CONSTITUING PART OF A FORM ON OUR WEBSITE, YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA FOR THE PURPOSES STATED IN THE PRIVACY STATEMENT.(d) Contact usThe personal data provided by yourself when contacting us via the contact form on the website or when contacting us by e-mail provided in the e-mail will only be processed in order to handle your contact request and stored for any further supplementary questions for a maximum duration of one year. Data processing for any other purposes does not take place.(e) NewsletterYou can subscribe to our newsletter via our website by entering your e-mail address, first and last name, and country of origin.BY CLICKING THE "SUBSCRIBE NOW" BUTTON, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE SUBSCRIPTION OF THE NEWSLETTER AND YOU ACCEPT OUR GENERAL TERMS OF USE.You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter and following the instructions on the unsubscribe page.Your data will be stored for the duration of your existing newsletter subscription and will be erased after the subscription is cancelled.(f) Your rightsYou are entitled to confirmation and communication of your personal data processed by us, as well as to rectification, erasure and restriction of the processing of personal data, the right of data portability and the right to object.You may withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time. The withdrawal of consent on your part shall not affect the lawfulness of processing of your personal data based on consent before its withdrawal. You can declare your withdrawal by sending an e-mail to dataprotection(at)erber-group.net.You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe that the processing of your personal data violates data protection law or your data protection claims have been violated in any other way. In Austria, this is the data protection authority ("Datenschutzbehörde").(g) Data protection reference in connection with links of third partiesWhere you use a link from this site to another please note that the other site's privacy policies may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or their observance at any other site.Use of CookiesTo optimize our website and services, we use Third Party Cookies and Remarketing-Tags on this website for "Google Adwords-Remarketing". Based on these tags on our system, personal information can be used as a filter criterion. However, your personal data will never be transmitted to third parties.Cookies are small text files that a web server sends to your browser when visiting a website. The text files contain data from previously visited websites that your browser saves while browsing.(a) Consent to the use of CookiesWhen you access our website for the first time, a clearly visible reference about the use of cookies appears asking you to consent to the use of cookies while visiting the website. You will simultaneously be provided with a link to our Terms and Conditions, which contain all necessary information about the different types and purposes of the cookies used by our website, in order to inform yourself about the nature and purpose of the data processing.BY CLICKING THE "ACCEPT COOKIES" BUTTON, YOU EXPRESSLY ACCEPT THE DATA PROCESSING AS DESCRIBED BELOW. You may withdraw your consent at any time (click here for details). However, as some types of cookies are essential for our site to operate, deactivating cookies may affect the functionality and performance of this website and its related services.(b) Types and manners of use of CookiesThe following cookies are used by www.biomin.net, whereby both Permanent Cookies (these cookies remain on your device even after closing the browser, until they are either automatically erased according to their settings or manually removed), as also Session Cookies (these temporary cookies are only temporarily stored and erased when closing the browser) are used:WWW.BIOMIN.NET COOKIES:Service/ProviderCookie NameDescription/PurposeMax. Storage Periodaddthis.com__atuvc __atuvs __atsscCookies that are set by the social sharing platform AddThis to track clicks and shares of a page.AddThis Privacy Policy30 dayssharethis.com__unamCookie that is set by the social sharing platform ShareThis to track the clicks and shares of a page.ShareThis Privacy Policy9 monthsGoogle Analytics__ga __gid __gat __utma __utmt __utmb __utmc __utmz __utmv _gaexpCookies used by the Google Analytics tracking tool to measure and optimize user behaviour.Google Analytics Cookie Overview50 monthsGoogle Adwords Remarketing Service used to capture visited pages within our website for the optimization of our online advertising campaigns. The user data is collected under aliases and no personal or sensitive data is stored.Google Privacy Policy Facebook Tracking Pixel The visitor action pixel of Facebook serves to measure the effectiveness of our marketing activities via the social network (Facebook). The data are stored on Facebook and recorded anonymously by us. The data collection only affects users who have an account on Facebook and are logged into the members area of Facebook. Users who are not members of Facebook are not affected by this data processing.Facebook Privacy Policy LinkedIn Insight Tag The LinkedIn Insight Tag enables the collection of metadata such as IP address information, timestamp, and events (e.g. page views). All data is encrypted. The LinkedIn browser cookie is stored in a user's browser until a user deletes the cookie or the cookie expires (there’s a rolling six-month expiration from the last time the user’s browser loaded the Insight Tag). Users have full control to block or delete cookies.LinkedIn Privacy Policy6 monthsHubspotList of cookiesCookies used by our marketing automation software (Hubspot) to track user behavior within our website. Personal and demographic data are collected and processed. For more information please visit this page.Hubspot Privacy Policy biomin.netcookiePolicyCookie for confirming the cookie indication.24 hoursbiomin.netfe_typo_userCookie of our Web Content Management System (TYPO3), which is used to identify user settings within a session. No personal data will be used for this purpose.Session Cookie (erased when closing the browser) (c) Blocking and erasure of Cookies, revocation of consent to the use of CookiesYou can prevent the use of cookies at any time by changing the settings in your browser. Already set cookies can be erased by changing the settings in your browser history. For more information on how to carry out these setting amendments, see:Microsoft Internet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookiesMozilla Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-storedGoogle Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en-GBApple Safari: https://support.apple.com/en-gb/guide/safari/sfri11471/maciPhone & iPad: https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265
